### **HOUSSAM**

#### **EL ISSIOUI**





**Phone Number** 

+212 679 76 64 19

Address

Lot Iguider IMM 139 NR 18 Avenue Allal

El Fassi Marrakech

E-mail

houssam-prof@hotmail.fr

## Skills

MS Office	••••	Tailwind CSS	••••
Google Ads	• • • • •	PHP Laravel	••••
Photoshop	•••00	React /Redux	••••
Illustrator	• • • 0 0	Flutter	••••
Adobe XD	••000	Node JS	••••
.NET / SQL server	•••00	Firebase	•••00

# languages

French Spanish	• • • • •
Spanish	
	• • • • •
Arabic	





### About me

Houssam El Issioui , a Morrocan 21 years old gratuated from Fsjes Marrakech university , and achieved online certifications such as front end developpement from Sololearn academy and Google Ads certifications . About my behavior, I'm very motivated to apply what I gained from the knowledges and experiences in the fields of Management and digital Marketing to be more developed so that I can consistently achieve better results. I'm also a challenging ,talented person and I understand the importance of being interactive and enjoy communicating with other co-workers for the benefit of the company.

### Education

University 2019 - 2022

Licence Degree in International Business Management and Marketing in Cadi-Ayyad University Marrakech .

2022: Advance 3 English level at Amecican language center ALC

University 2020 - 2022

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development and Computer Networking at college Racine Marrakech.

Bachelor 2018 - 2020

2020: Baccalaureate degree in Literature and humanitarian sciences with Honors (independent candidate).

2018: Baccalaureate degree in Physics and Chemistry sciences

Certification 2019 - 2022

Google Ads certifications: Search/Display ID: 89348596/

88767274

Sololearn: React + Redux CT-72SUJLAL Issued 08 november 2022

## Experience

Work August 2022 - October 2022

worked as a web Designer in LoyalTec S.A.R.L taking mission of developping creative E-commerce Landing Pages for increasing the purshace of the multiproducts and services offered by the company Ex:www.prixchock.com / www.aurafrica.shop

Work January 2021 - September 2021

worked as an intern in Enajd-info Technologie S.A.R.L being a marketing seller of computer hardware products to active and potential customers also to solving Issues related to the maintenance of operating systems installed on the company.

Work June 2019 - February 2020

Worked as an intern secretary in Equipement bureautique et formation el idrissi EBFI S.A.R.L society sharing responsibility of multiple tasks ( cashier, selling products, E.R.P inventory management ,entry of purchase orders).